for those who prefer Linux or are simply
对于那些喜欢 Linux或简单的人来说
curious about Linux and other open
对Linux和其他开放感到好奇
source technologies this is category 5
源技术这是第5类
technology TV
技术电视
you
您
273 of category 5 technology wild
类别5技术野生的 273
reading world hello I'm fabulous I'm
阅读世界你好我很棒我是
proud to be here fun bit of a mix-up I
很荣幸能够在这里与我混合一起
didn't know which day it was which month
不知道哪一天是哪个月
it was when i'm supposed to come yeah
那是我应该来的时候
I'm here thank you yes everybody the
我在这里非常感谢你
chat room tons of people presently
聊天室现在吨人
chatting away from the World Wide World
聊天离开世界各地
tech guru Oh No can you hear me now
高科技大师哦，不，你现在能听到我的声音吗？
anybody can hear me now welcome to the
任何人都可以听到我现在欢迎来
show River removable rewind what episode
显示河可移动倒带什么情节
is it what day is it three eleventh of
现在是三点十一分
December nice to see you everybody
十二月很高兴见到你们每个人
thanks chat room we love having you here
感谢聊天室，我们喜欢你在这里
and watching out for us you are like her
并留意我们，你就像她一样
you don't even need to hire audio
你甚至不需要雇用音频
engineers anymore because the guys in
工程师了，因为那些家伙
the shower we like ads right there
我们喜欢那里的广告
rookie something's going on with your
菜鸟正在与你的事情发生关系
mic there maybe it's not even plugged in
麦克风，可能它甚至没有插入
just saying so yeah hey Rob Gore Carly
只是说罗伯戈尔卡莉嘿嘿
nice to see ya what's ready everybody
很高兴看到雅什么是 每个人都做好准备
they're coming to us from Chicago chart
他们从芝加哥图表来到我们这里
near Charleston West Virginia that's in
在查尔斯顿西弗吉尼亚州附近
the Americas ridge inc where's the world
美洲岭公司在哪里的世界
wide world you are watching all over
你正在看遍世界广
where are you watching from and
你从哪里看？
certainly if you're new here make sure
当然如果你是新来的，确保
you say hi in the chat room its category
你在聊天室里打个招呼
5 on freenode or of course you can visit
5在freenode或当然你可以访问
our website category 5 TV click on
我们的网站类别5电视点击
interact and join the chat room hey JP
互动并加入聊天室嘿JP
Rob gore's watching from Melbourne
罗布戈尔从墨尔本看着
Australia nice to see ya Carly's
澳大利亚很高兴看到你卡莉的
watching from here and Barry who hey
从这里看Barry和嘿
Barry yeah that's one for Barry we are
巴里是的，这是巴里我们的一个
up three points tonight 4 points or
今晚4分或3分
points for Barry hey
巴里嘿点
we are winning here Rob gar it's pretty
我们在这里赢得罗布加尔，它很漂亮
fabulous having everybody pressure over
令人难以置信的让所有人都感到压力
yeah anyways I got some news I'm gonna
无论如何，我得到了一些我要去的消息
tell you a little bit of a teaser right
告诉你一点点传闻权
now what you can expect in a just a
现在你可以期待什么，只是一个
brief while coming up in the newsroom a
在编辑室出现时简要介绍一下
virgin Galactic spaceship will cater to
处女银河飞船将迎合
both passengers and scientists yes what
乘客和科学家都是
if you fall under both of those
如果你属于这两者
classifications then you better chance
分类，那么你更好的机会
definitely better chance excellente yes
肯定更好的机会是好的
definitely Oh a new IBM chip will use
绝对是一个新的IBM芯片将会使用的
light to speed up communications with
加快与之沟通
apps and other net services hmm google
应用程序和其他网络服务嗯谷歌
had a pretty bad cloud outage yesterday
昨天有一个非常糟糕的云中断
which we're going to talk about a little
我们将会谈一点
bit more I felt that yeah as well
还有一点我觉得 是的
Twitter and Instagram are parting ways
Twitter和Instagram正在分道扬ways
but no worries twitter has its own
但不用担心twitter有它自己的问题
Instagram killer and lastly MIT
Instagram杀手，最后是麻省理工学院
scientists have developed an early model
科学家已经开发出一种早期模型
shape-shifting robot sir Graham cuz
变形机器人先生Graham cuz
these stories are coming up later in our
这些故事是在我们后来出现的
show that sounds cool uh-huh hey I got
表明， 听起来很酷呃，嘿，我得到了
to say greets to Dave May do who's
向戴夫·梅表示问候
joining us in the chat room as well
加入我们的聊天室
tonight great to see ya where are you
今晚很高兴看到你在哪里
been yeah we're glad you're there no we
是的，我们很高兴你在那里没有我们
are always miss yet drumstick nice to
总是想念但鼓槌很好
see you again as well yeah I see like
再次见到你，是的，我看到了
tons of people from all over the world
来自 世界各地的许多人
here it's pretty sweet yeah we like to
在这里，我们很喜欢它
talk to people from around the world in
与来自世界各地的人们交谈
the chat room we also like to get
聊天室我们也很喜欢
people's postcards from around the world
来自世界各地的人们的明信片
you sure do and he'll how can they send
你当然可以，他会怎么发送
those in send your postcards or maybe
那些寄你的明信片或者可能
belated Christmas cards to category 5
迟到的圣诞贺卡至第5类
technology TV p.o.box to 9009 very
技术电视pobox到9009非常
Ontario which of course is in Canada l 4
安大略当然是在加拿大l 4
&amp; 7 w 7 we would love to hear from you
＆7 7我们很乐意听取 您的意见
that way we've got our lovely wall of
这样我们就有了我们可爱的墙
it's a beautiful collage of cards and
这是一个美丽的卡和拼贴画
trinkets and pictures from around the
饰品和来自各地的图片
world from viewers like you we love it
来自我们喜欢的观众的世界
birthday greetings go out to Chris Reich
生日祝福出现在Chris Reich身上
tonight happy birthday happy 29th man
今晚生日快乐快乐的第29个男人
thanks for spending your birthday with
谢谢你的生日
us yeah
我们是的
it's a nice day for you but happy
对你来说这是一个美好的一天，但很开心
birthday my friend nice to see ya
生日我的朋友很高兴见到你
totally totally awesome guess 6590 is
完全完全真棒猜测6590是
joining us live tonight from Naples
加入我们今晚从那不勒斯生活
Florida cool great to have you here
佛罗里达很酷很高兴有你在这里
uh-huh lots of lots of friends that's
嗯，很多朋友都是这样的
fasho we like it we love it Rob gore
fasho我们喜欢它 我们爱它Rob gore
says show us the postcard wall show us
说给我们看明信片墙给我们看
the postcard wall if you're watching
明信片墙，如果你正在 看
backstage pass you can see the postcard
后台通行证你可以看到明信片
wall yes you can or if you go to our
墙是的，你可以或如果你去我们的
website category 5 TV there is a picture
网站类别5电视有一张照片
of it for you oh cool yeah and I think
对你来说哦，酷，是的，我想
that is let's see here I'll find it for
是 让我们看到这里我会找到它
you that would be great yes it's it is
你会那么好，就是这样
really cool like I'm looking at it right
真的很酷， 就像我在 看它的权利
now I see it's like a little bit of a
现在我看到它像 的 一点点
little bit of history all of our friends
我们所有的朋友都有一点历史
yes that means so much to receive them
是的，这意味着要接收它们
for sure Dolph like little highlights of
对于Dolph来说确实很像
your town that's cool where you're from
你的城镇很酷，你来自哪里
we'd send you a berry postcard but it's
我们会寄给你一张浆果明信片，但它是
not exciting it is exciting it's just
不令人兴奋，这是令人兴奋的
that it would it would take two weeks to
这将需要两周的时间
get here anyway and it's Barry and it's
无论如何，这是巴里，它是
a local like I could just hand deliver
一个像我可以交付的地方
it the studio right true not the berries
它的工作室是正确的不是浆果
not exciting it's just well to each
并不令人兴奋，这对每个人都很好
their own or something like that I'm
他们自己或类似的东西
trying to remember where I put in fact
试图记住我放哪儿 其实
her the postcard wall i don't know if i
她的明信片墙我不知道我是否
put it up on our flickr channel or it is
把它放在我们的flickr频道或它
oh you know what it's probably on our
哦，你知道我们的可能是什么
facebook channel cuz that's where
Facebook频道cuz，这是在哪里
everything tends to go there is a
一切都倾向于去那里
picture on our flickr channel that kind
图片 在我们的 flickr频道那种
of shows it this is a behind the scenes
显示它这是幕后
from a while ago yes and you can see
从前不久， 你可以看到
that there is the postcard wall right
明信片墙是正确的
there so that's what the studio looks
那么这就是演播室的外观
like from heathers perspective and
从学者的角度来看
that's on our flickr photo gallery on
这是在我们的flickr照片库上
our website yeah very very cool sweet
我们的网站是非常非常酷的甜蜜
yeah okay so tonight we were planning to
没关系，今晚我们打算这么做
look at this brother printer I know if
看看这个兄弟打印机， 我知道如果
you're following me on Twitter and and
你在Twitter和and上跟踪我
through Facebook and if you're watching
通过Facebook，如果你正在观看
the the show's calendar at cap five dot
该节目的日历在 第五点
TV / calendar it's really really
电视/日历这真的是真的
exciting that we're gonna be looking at
令人兴奋的是，我们会看着
the the brand new business smart line of
全新的商业智能系列
printers from brother this is a
兄弟打印机这是一个
they're their latest and greatest it's
他们是他们的最新和最伟大的
got the super high yield cartridges it's
得到了超高容量的墨盒
crazy awesome I I want to like lift this
疯狂真棒II想要解除这个问题
up and show it to you because it is
并展示 给你，因为它是
lightweight you see that is I see it I
轻量级，你看到， 我看到它
they have made probably the sleekest
他们已经做出了最可怕的事情
printer that I've seen in a long time
我很久以前看过的打印机
but you see how small and lightweight
但你会看到小巧轻便
this is yeah yeah it prints 11 x 17
这是耶是打印11×17
really figure that out we're going to be
真的明白我们将会是什么
looking at that now we wanted to look at
看，现在我们想看看
that this week but unfortunately the it
本周，但不幸的是它
didn't work out because there's there is
没有工作，因为那里有
an interview involved and unfortunately
一次采访涉及并且不幸
we there's some sickness a flu going
我们有一些疾病感染流感
around at the other end so so we're
在另一端，所以我们是
going to have our guests joining us
让我们的客人加入我们
again instead next week so hey make sure
下周再来，所以嘿确保
you watch for but you see that beautiful
你注意，但你看到那美丽
printer it's got a scanner fax touch
打印机它有一个扫描仪传真触摸
screen color touchscreen huh Prince 11 x
屏幕彩色触摸屏王子11 x
17 it's got the sheet feeder it is
17它有它的送纸器
duplexing so that means it automatically
双工，这意味着它自动
flips to the other side all in that
所有这一切都翻转到另一边
little lightweight thing that's cool and
轻巧的东西，很酷，而且
we're gonna be giving one away for
我们会送一个去的
Christmas so can I get out of this
圣诞节，我可以摆脱 这一点
that's good you don't want to miss out
这很好，你不想错过
on next week's show well that's awesome
在下周的节目中，这真是太棒了
it's a it's an ink-jet Reb D Jenk but it
这是一个喷墨Reb D Jenk，但它
has four cartridges so you've got the
有四个墨盒，您已经得到了
CMYK so you don't have to worry about
CMYK，所以你不必担心
you know if you run at a yellow ink
你知道如果你用黄色墨水跑
having to replace the whole color
必须替换整个颜色
cartridge is just the yellow cartridge
墨盒只是黄色墨盒
interesting hmm Wow okay well that'll be
有趣的嗯哇好吧，那会
a sweet show I'm excited for that
一个甜蜜的表演，我为此感到兴奋
definitely so what are we doing tonight
绝对如此， 我们今晚做了什么
instead we are going to be looking at
相反，我们将会看到
how to create our very own custom
如何创建我们自己的习惯
calendar o 12 month calendar and we're
历O 12个月的日历和我们
going to start by creating one for
将开始 创建一个
category 5 TV and when we create it
5类电视以及我们创作的时间
you're actually gonna be able to get
你实际上能够得到
yourself one so let's stick around we're
你自己一个，所以我们坚持我们
gonna be showing you how to do that it
会告诉你如何做到这 一点
makes a great gift oh yeah I mean
是一个伟大的礼物哦是的，我的意思是
pictures of the kids grandma's love that
孩子们奶奶的爱的照片
sort of thing absolutely they eat it up
他们绝对会把它吃掉
it's perfect so stick around we're gonna
它是完美的，所以坚持我们会
be looking at all that and we've got
看着这一切，我们有
your viewer questions as well love to
您的观众问题以及爱
receive those and we're going to be
接收这些，我们将成为
addressing those shortly if you've got a
如果你有一个问题很快解决这些问题
mobile device bring up mcat five dot TV
移动设备带来mcat五点电视
and you'll be able to bring that up on
你就可以把这个 提升起来
your device that's our mobile website
您的设备是我们的移动网站
very cool stuff and it of course gives
非常酷的东西，它当然给
you access to the show through your
你通过你的节目访问节目
smart
聪明
town very very cool yes all right well
镇非常非常酷是的一切都很好
we've got to take a really quick break
我们必须采取 一个非常快速突破
before we talk about how to create our
在我们讨论如何创建我们的产品之前
calendar and we've got your viewer
日历，我们有你的观众
questions coming up in a little while
问题在一段时间后出现
and all those great stories that
和所有那些伟大的故事
Hillary's going to be talking about I
希拉里将会谈论我
want to learn about this shape-shifting
想要了解这种形状转换
robot as do I dance your interest in
机器人，因为我跳舞你的兴趣
robots so stick around we'll be right
机器人如此坚持我们会是对的
back after this join category 5
回到这个加入类别5之后
technology TV on December 25th for our
科技电视12月25日为我们的
Christmas special with musical
圣诞节特别与音乐
performances by our on-air team plus a
我们的直播团队演出加上a
special guest performance by our co-host
由我们的共同主持人特别嘉宾表演
from seasons one and two Karrie Webb
从第一季和第二季Karrie Webb
don't miss the Christmas special Tuesday
周二不要错过圣诞节的特别节目
December 25th at seven p.m. eastern time
12月25日东部时间晚上七点
ww category five TV
ww 五类电视
at eco alkalines we believe you should
在生态碱我们相信你应该
be able to trust your batteries not just
不仅能够信任你的电池
here but here here and here but with one
这里，但在这里，在这里， 但有一个
exception you should also be able to
异常你也应该 能够
trust your batteries here eco alkalines
相信你的电池在这里生态碱
of the world's first and only certified
世界上第一个也是唯一的认证
carbon neutral battery manufactured to
碳中性电池制造
the highest standards of recycling and
回收再利用的最高标准
quality without any trace amounts of
质量没有任何痕量的
harmful chemicals like mercury lead or
有害的化学物质，如汞铅或汞
cadmium eco outlines provide performance
镉生态轮廓提供性能
that rivals leading national alkaline
该国对手领先的全国碱性
battery brands at a comparable price
可比价格的电池品牌
find out more about the Eco alkalines
了解有关生态碱的更多信息
difference eco alkalines calm this is
不同的生态碱冷静这是
category 5 technology TV episode number
第5类技术电视剧集号码
273 thanks for joining us I'm Robbie
273感谢加入我们，我是罗比
Ferguson I'm Hillary Rumble keeping it
弗格森我是希拉里鲁布保持它
real over here Hillary before we get
在我们得到之前，真正在这里的希拉里
into our feature creating a calendar I
进入我们的功能创建一个日历我
want to show you something okay so super
想要告诉你一些好的事情如此超级
cool i love cool thanks for all the geek
酷我非常感谢所有的极客
freaks out there dream dream land from
从那里梦寐以求的梦幻之地
brent Spiner oh yeah what I thought was
布伦特·斯派尔噢我认为 是
cool and you know who pence per day I
很酷，你知道我每天的便士
know but I'm waiting for it I know but I
知道但我正在等待 它我知道但 我
don't know check this out yes Heather
不知道检查出希瑟
wins okay I knew I'm like I recognize
赢得好，我知道我就像我承认
that name but I can't figure out
那个名字，但我无法弄清楚
personally autographed this is actually
其实亲自亲笔签名
autograph you can get it off of his
你可以从他的签名中得到它
website the real brent Spiner calm I
网站真正的布伦特Spiner 冷静我
thought that was impressive that I was
我以为这 是 令人印象深刻的
going to get this so excited about this
会让这个如此兴奋
but look at this sent it in an envelope
但看看这个发送它在一个信封
and the geek and me is so excited about
和怪胎和我是如此兴奋
that I did yes he actually signed the
我确实是他实际签署了
envelope himself Wow how do you like
信封自己哇你怎么样
that really cool so he has on CD he's
这真的很酷，所以他已经在CD上了
got a couple CDs is actually a bit of a
有一对CD实际上是一个
crooner he's he's really good ah yes
他是他的好兄弟，是的
that's good we love brent Spiner so yeah
这很好，我们爱布伦特Spiner所以是的
Lieutenant Commander data from star trek
来自星际迷航的中校司令官的数据
right yes yes yes mm-hmm now I recall
是的是的是的，是的， 我现在回想起来
sorry everyone don't get mad fine i love
对不起，每个人都不会因为我爱而生气
you i knew i knew the name i just
你， 我知道我知道这个名字，我 只是
couldn't remember oh i haven't talked in
不记得哦， 我还没有 说话
a few weeks oh I'm just kidding hey
几个星期哦，我只是在开玩笑嘿
Jamison gets it well it was 25 bucks for
贾米森得到它很好，这是25美元
the CD and he signed it and everything
CD和他签署了一切
but interesting that he actually stood
但有趣的是他实际上站了起来
yeah
是啊
and the post office and said oh I
和邮局说哦我
actually did another one of these
实际上做了另一个这些
another one of these Trek nerds has
另一个这些Trek书呆子了
bought my CD hahahahaha you know and
买了我的CD哈哈哈哈哈你知道和
then mailed it on Sunday that's cool
然后在星期天邮寄它很酷
yeah good well I've got to the
好，我已经到了
collection of Awesome well I can't throw
非常棒的集合 我不能扔
away the envelope oh that's cool yeah
离开信封哦，这很酷是的
just can't believe that's just clutter
只是不能相信这只是混乱
that's his autograph yeah you have it
这是他的亲笔签名是的，你有它
twice not once but twice once once sent
两次一次但两次一次发送
directly to me hello yeah okay so
直接给我，你好耶没关系
tonight we want to create an actual
今晚我们想创造一个真实的
calendar with our own photos and so I've
日历与我们自己的照片，所以我已经
actually created a little bit of a
实际创建的一点点
collection of photos from you know
收集你的照片知道
category yeah really when you want to
类别是真的当你想要
create a calendar what's the first thing
创建一个日历什么是第一件事
you got to do you got to find 12 photos
你必须要找到12张照片
or something like that you need one for
或者你需要的东西
every month if you're going to do a
每个月， 如果你打算 做一个
one-year care so in my case I'm also
一年护理，所以在我的情况下，我也是
going to do a couple of collages so we
我们会去做几个拼贴
might have like a Hillary Rumble page
可能像Hillary Rumble页面一样
and it's got three pictures of Hillary
它有三张希拉里的照片
right so so what we'll do we're gonna
对，所以我们会做我们会做的
bring up a website called Lulu Lulu yeah
建立一个名为Lulu Lulu的网站是的
lulu.com calm and once we're there we're
lulu.com冷静，一旦我们在那里，我们就是
gonna hit sign up up here and really
会在这里注册，真的
quickly we're going to create an account
很快我们要创建一个帐户
looks good to me mm-hmm well there we go
我看起来不错- 嗯 ，我们走吧
good strong pass yes good job always
总是好的传球是好的
strong passwords you want notifications
你想要通知的强密码
I'll turn it off just cuz then they're
我会把它关掉只是 因为他们是
gonna get our autoresponder every night
每天晚上都会得到我们的自动回复
okay signed up and good to go we're
好吧，注册好，我们很好
logged in this category 5 technology TV
登录此类别 5技术电视
cool let's publish so first thing now
酷现在让我们首先发布
you see that Lulu does some other stuff
你看到Lulu做了一些其他的事情
to books ebooks photo books photo books
到书籍 电子书照片书照片书
very cool thing if you're into that you
非常酷的事情，如果你进入你的
know making an actual photo books take
知道如何制作实际的照片书
some wedding photos you know and and put
一些婚礼照片，你知道和把
them together in a really nice kind of
他们在一起非常好
portfolio looking thing with the printed
组合看印刷的东西
directly on the page they do a really
直接在他们真正做的页面上
really nice job you can see you know
真的很好，你可以看到你知道
from the website here it's it's really
从网站这里是真的
professional stuff I'll click on photo
专业的东西， 我会点击照片
books just so you can see kind of
只有你才能看到书籍
another project for another day there
另一个项目在那里
you go for another day but for tonight
你去另一天，但 今晚
you can go to calendars and we're
你可以去日历，我们
actually going to create our calendar so
实际上将创建我们的日历
you can choose whether you want a
你可以选择你是否想要一个
standard size which 11 x 17 open or a
标准尺寸，11 x 17开放或a
premium size which is 13.5 x 19 inches
优质尺寸为13.5 x 19英寸
so that's quite large you see that that
所以这很大，你看到了
starts at 2549 whereas the smaller one
从2549开始，而较小的一个
which is the regular size calendars only
这只是常规 尺寸的日历
1399 so we'll do that one ok ok so I've
1399所以我们会这样做一个好的，所以我已经
single clicked on it and go start
单击它并开始
creating so as I said I've already kind
就像我说的我已经很友善一样创造
of gone through my photos and picked out
通过我的照片， 并挑选出来
some that are gonna work and I've
有些是会工作，我已经
labeled them you know january-february
标记他们你知道1月 -  2月
oh sorry April there's March is gonna be
哦，对不起四月有三月会是
your collage may-july kind of thing
你的拼贴可能是7月的事情
right so we can take a picture like this
正确的，所以我们可以采取这样的图片
will actually be making that's gonna and
实际上会做出这样的决定
we'll be putting that together in a
我们将把它们放在一起
counter so that's just loading up there
计数器，所以这只是在那里加载
this is all this is what's neat about
这是这一切是何等的整洁约
you know the modern web is everything is
你知道现代网络就是一切
done through your web browser hmm we
通过您的网络浏览器完成嗯，我们
don't need to fly software to be able to
不需要飞软件就可以
do this not anymore I remember when you
不要再这样做我记得当你
used to have to like your special Saint
曾经不得不喜欢你特别的圣人
like by certain CDs to like just to get
就像某些CD 想要得到的一样
clipart right I need and then you still
剪贴画权利我需要，然后你仍然
have to find something to print it yeah
必须找到一些 打印它是的
I was probably getting in the car with
我可能在车里上车
it on a CD or a floppy disk yeah and
它在CD或软盘上是啊和
taking awesome
采取真棒
yeah having a printed now it's all done
是啊，现在打印完成了
in one place oh so it's all done through
在一个地方哦，这一切都完成了
your web browser is so easy breezy so
您的网页浏览器如此轻松愉快
looking at this there are many many
看这个有很多很多
templates that you can use these are
你可以使用这些模板
themes that Lulu provides for you and
Lulu为你和你提供的主题
you can see that you can basically just
你可以看到 你基本上可以
pick one that you like if you want to
选一个你喜欢的，如果你想
take you know the real easy way out so
让你知道真正简单的出路
to speak you can choose one of these
说话你可以选择其中之一
themes that kind of already lay out your
这种主题已经奠定了你的
photos in a fancy way with a background
照片以一种奇特的方式与背景
behind them and looks like some kind of
在他们身后，看起来像某种
a cutaway you know these kinds of things
你知道这些事情的剖面图
and it looks really professional but for
它看起来 很专业，但对于
me I want to actually fill the whole
我想要实际填补整个
page so this one with the puppy is
这页与小狗是一样的
called modern and you can see that the
所谓的现代，你可以看到 ，
picture is in fact going to fill the
图片实际上是要填补的
entire page so that's the one that I
整个页面，所以这是我的
want this is I that gives me a little
希望这是我给了我一点
bit more control you can choose
多一点的控制， 你可以选择
whichever one you like so you can either
无论你喜欢哪一个， 你 都可以
upload your photos of this step or
上传这一步的照片或
alternatively you can upload them at the
或者你可以上传他们的
next step and kind of lay them out I
下一步， 并把它们摆放出来
prefer to just go next choose my dates
宁愿 只是去选择我的日期
so I've not uploaded any photos date
所以我没有上传任何照片的日期
range January 2013 to December 2013 of
范围2013年1月至2013年12月
course that's going to be a standard
当然这将是一个标准
calendar for for the year of 2013 but
日历为2013年，但
you can change you know what month you
你可以改变你知道你的月份
wanted to end on you can make it a two
想结束你可以让它成为两个
year calendar if you wanted to it's
如果你想要的话，可以选择日历
going to increase the cost based on how
基于如何增加成本
many pages we'll just do a full one year
很多页面我们只会 做一整年
starting from January ending in December
从一月份到十二月结束
next we'll set events so let's say okay
接下来我们将设置事件，让我们说 好吧
we're going to add new Hillary your
我们将添加新的希拉里你的
birthday please july 19th so we're gonna
生日请7月19日，所以我们会去的
go like this so that everybody knows to
这样去大家都知道
celebrate on that very special day
在那个特别的日子庆祝
Friday sweet every year and save so
星期五甜蜜，每年都如此
Hillary's birthday will come up there
希拉里的生日将会出现在那里
robbie's birthday very close to mine
罗比的生日非常接近我的
yeah we're actually we're like birthday
是的，我们其实就像生日那样
twins july 17 for wednesday super close
双胞胎7月17日星期三超级密切
and notice i've set that to every year
并注意到 我已经设定了每年
the reason that I've done that is so
我这样做的原因是如此
that if I do create a calendar for next
如果我确实为下一个创建日历
year it will automatically put my
一年它会自动把我的
birthday's in
生日在
nice amazing night so that's pretty cool
不错的惊人夜晚，所以这很酷
so that gets us started with a couple of
所以让我们开始了几个
different events you can put in anything
不同的事件你可以放入任何东西
that you like so we're gonna go see your
你喜欢我们会去看看 你的
calendar you can also add public
日历你也可以添加公共
holidays I don't know if you saw that or
假期我不知道你是否看到过或
not I'll just show you quickly again
不，我会再次快速地告诉你
public holidays pretty cool if you're
公共假期很酷，如果你是
making this for Canada only you can
只有你才能做到这一点
check off Canada and it will actually
检查加拿大，它会实际上
add Canadian holidays to your calendar
将加拿大节日添加到日历中
for you automatically that's cool I've
对你来说，这很酷，我已经
opted against nap because we're gonna
选择反对小睡，因为我们会去的
we're building something for you know
我们正在为你建立一些东西
the viewers that you yourself may wanna
你自己可能想要的观众
put up in the wall we've got viewers all
放在墙上我们都有观众
over the world so if I Canadian holidays
如果我加拿大的假期在世界各地
it's it's off for you at home so we'll
它在家里关闭了，所以我们会
leave that out but we'll put our
离开这一点，但我们会把我们的
birthdays and show episodes and things
生日和秀节目和事情
like that on there so so we'll leave
就像在那里，所以我们会离开
that but you can add that to your
但你可以添加到你的
calendar so there's what the front of my
日历，所以我的前面是什么
calendar looks like so far pretty plain
日历看起来非常简单
you can see there's looking at the
你可以看到有人在看
inside of the calendar see what I've
在日历里面看看我的
done is I've just simply clicked on a
完成是我只是简单地点击一个
month down to the bottom here
一个月到这里的底部
january-february march right down here
一月 - 二月游行就在这里
okay so let's start with January and
好吧，让我们从一 月份 开始
you'll see that if i zoom in using the
你会看到， 如果我放大使用
zoom tool down here you can in fact read
放大缩小工具在这里你可以实际阅读
what's what's in there and you'll see
那里有什么，你会看到
that for the full size it's asking for a
对于全尺寸它要求一个
3375 pixel x 26 25 pixel ok pretty sure
3375像素×26像素25 OK相当 肯定
you can see that at home so that's if I
你可以在家里看到，如果我是这样的话
want it to fill the entire page just
希望它只填充整个页面
like the picture did now I can also up
像现在的照片我也可以起来
at the left hand side here I can choose
在左边我可以选择
these different grid patterns ok I see
这些不同的网格模式确定我看到了
so if I'd like I can go with this grid
所以如果我想我可以去这个网格
pattern and now it's going to break up
模式，现在它将分手
my calendar in such a way see if I got
我的日历以这种方式看我是否得到
it oh yeah ok so now instead of that one
它哦，好吧现在，而不是那一个
great big area I've got a larger area at
伟大的大面积我有一个更大的面积
the left which is 2142 by 26 25 and then
左边是2142乘2625，然后
a couple of areas on the right one of
在右边的几个区域
them is 12 13 and the other one is to
他们是12 13 ，另一个是
just a little bit of a different height
只是一点点不同的 高度
ok so you can set up your own grid
好吧，你可以建立你自己的网格
patterns like that and it allows you to
这样的模式，它可以让你
really you know place you know if you're
如果你真的知道你知道的地方
doing pictures
拍照
kids you have one really nice picture
孩子你有一个非常好的图片
and then a picture of the dog and a
然后是一张狗和一张照片
picture of a toy or something next to it
玩具的图片或者它旁边的东西
it gives a real kind of almost a
它给了一个真正的几乎一个
scrapbooking kind of feel to it so let's
剪贴簿的感觉，让我们来
start with just a single photo that's
从一张照片开始
going to fill the entire page so now
现在要填满整个页面
over here at the right I'm going to go
在这里右边我要去
ad images and I'm going to go upload
广告图片和我要去上传
your images go into that folder where
你的图像进入那个文件夹
I've got all those pictures and I'm
我有这些照片， 我是
going to grab the team photo from
要抓住来自队伍的照片
January for january this is the one that
一月一月，这 是一个
I picked so it's going to upload that
我选择了它会上传
nice and simple now this is just telling
这很好，很简单，现在这只是告诉
me that hey you know what this is a
我嘿，你 知道这 是 什么
multi tasking website you can either
多任务网站，你可以
wait or you can keep on working and you
等待或者你可以继续工作，你
can actually keep working and that it
实际上可以继续工作，它
will do your upload in the background
会在后台做你的上传
which is pretty awesome so it works very
这非常棒，所以它的工作非常
much like a multitasking environment
很像多任务环境
that you can work in I like to see kind
你可以工作，我喜欢看到善良
of the progress here so it's going going
在 这里 的 进展，所以它正在进行
going keep in mind that with Lulu when
请记住，与露露时
you're creating your calendars there is
你正在创建你的日历
a 10 megabyte limit to each image so if
每张图片都有10兆的限制，所以如果
you've created the images yourself in
你已经创建了自己的图像
the GIMP or Photoshop you want to make
您想要制作的GIMP或Photoshop
sure that they are at most 10 megs
确信他们最多只有10个兆
shouldn't be a problem because it's
应该不是问题，因为它
providing you with the dimensions that
为您提供尺寸
it wants some of the pictures that come
它想要一些来的照片
off of our camera because there's such
我们的相机因为有这样的关闭
high resolution if I edit them and then
高分辨率，如果我编辑他们， 然后
resave them as a JPEG with a hundred
将它们重新保存为一百张 JPEG
percent quality they're going to be
他们将会达到的质量百分比
something like 15 or 16 megs so then
然后像15或16 megs那样
they don't work so so that's something
他们不工作，所以这是一些东西
to keep in mind so these photos as you
要记住这些照片和你一样
see is there just six almost seven Meg's
看看是否只有六个近7 Meg的
so here goes almost there I can just hit
所以这里差不多可以打到
done if I want and it's going to show up
如果我想要，它会显示出来
over here it's a very easy to use
在这里它是一个非常容易使用
drag-and-drop kind of interface yeah and
拖放式的界面是啊和
you'll notice that I didn't actually
你会注意到我其实没有
scale this image that is uploading right
缩放正在上传的图像
now it is just strictly well I think i
现在， 我认为我的确很好
cropped it just to know I haven't even
裁剪它只是为了知道我甚至没有
cropped it so you see that there is you
裁剪它，让你看到有你
know some studio cloth at the right hand
知道右手一些工作室布
side there the edge of our drape you
那边我们的悬垂你的边缘
know so we'll actually crop that using
知道所以我们实际上会裁剪使用
Lulu instead of the GIMP in this
Lulu代替了GIMP
particular case so you see that it's
特别的情况下，你看到它
there okay so now I simply hold in and
没关系，现在我只是坚持和
drag it and drop it onto my canvas and
拖动它并将其放到我的画布上
it puts it in there in kind of a preview
它将它放在那里进行预览
mode and you'll see that it has already
模式，你会看到它已经
crop
作物
the edge because of the the way that it
因为它的缘故
has scaled it so if I'm not happy with
如果我不满意的话，已经缩放了它
the cropping I can actually just kind of
我实际上可能只是种植
zoom out a little bit so that I can see
缩小一点以便我可以看到
the whole canvas and single click on my
整个画布和单击我的
image and you see that there is an hour
图像，你看到 有一个小时
zoom tool that allows me to zoom in on
缩放工具，允许我放大
the photo and drag the photo around
照片并拖动照片
directly you know within my web browser
直接在我的网络浏览器中知道
there you go some photos that you load
你会看到你加载的一些照片
up might come in you know crooked or
你可能会知道歪了或
whatever so you can rotate them and then
无论如何你可以旋转它们然后
position them within your canvas so now
现在将它们定位在您的画布内
that that's done there's our January
那是在一月份完成的
cool so January's ready to go sweet and
酷，所以一月份准备好去甜蜜和
that's what it looks like ok skipping
这就是它看起来 好跳过
along so let's let's do March let's say
所以让我们来做三月吧
january-february March and we're gonna
一月 - 二月三月，我们会去的
do a let's do one of these collages that
做一个让我们做一个这样的拼贴画
I was saying about okay alrighty so what
我说 没关系 左右 这样alrighty什么
I've already done just to be prepared
我已经做好了准备
for this is we've got three pictures of
因为这是我们已经有了三个图片
Hillary here because March is going to
希拉里在这里是因为三月会去的
be Hillary's month so there's picture
是希拉里的月，所以有照片
number one picture number two and
第一张图片编号为2和
picture number three mmm okay good with
图片编号三mmm 好吧
that yeah alright so let's grab the one
那好吧，让我们抓住那个
that I've created for the left side and
我已经为左侧创建了
you'll see again that Lulu actually
实际上你会再次看到Lulu
gives you the dimensions that have wants
给你想要的尺寸
okay 2142 by 26 25 so using the GIMP we
好吧2142通过 26 25所以使用GIMP我们
can take the original photo let's maybe
可以拍下原始照片吧
do one just so that you see how it works
只是为了让你看到它是如何工作的
okay so this is the photo that I want to
好的，这是我想要的照片
use you know open this up in the GIMP
使用你 知道在 GIMP中 打开它
okay so I with this one I want to
好，所以我想用这一个
actually do a little bit of cropping
实际上做一点点修剪
myself I could just upload it and and
我自己我可以上传它和
then have you know do the kind of
那么你知道怎么做
stretch it out and do it that way but I
把它伸出去，这样做，但我
want to actually add a little bit of a
想要实际添加一点点
an effect to it to make it look nice so
对它的影响，使它看起来不错
instead of just having the raw photo
而不是仅仅有照片
from the camera where you can kind of
从相机哪里可以找到
you know see a couple of the wrinkles in
你知道看到一些皱纹
the drape behind you and things like
背后的帷幕和诸如此类的事物
that we want to kind of clean it up a
我们想要清理它
little bit so dimensions for this back
一点点这样尺寸这回
at Lulu are 2142 by 26 25 let's see if I
在露露是2142年26 25让我们看看我
can remember k file new
可以记住新的k文件
214 to buy 20 forget I tried to remember
214 买20忘记我试图记住
too nice see this is why I do like the
太好看看这就是为什么我喜欢这个
GIMP layout because I can move things
GIMP布局，因为我可以移动东西
around that is see behind it unlike
这与其背后看到的不一样
Photoshop where it's all one window okay
Photoshop哪里都是一个窗口 好吧
so I've created the dimensions of a new
所以我创建了一个新的维度
image now next thing very very important
现在形象下一件事情非常非常重要
go to Advanced Options and change it to
转到高级选项并将其更改为
300 DPI okay so that's the dots per inch
300 DPI 好，所以这是每英寸的点数
and then hit ok so now i have a canvas
然后点击OK，现在我有一个画布
which is going to perfectly fit within
这将 完全适合
the leftmost area of this particular
这个特定的最左边的区域
calendar so we're going to grab that
日历，所以我们要抓住它
photo and if we look at this photo this
照片，如果我们看这张照片这个
photo is 2472 pixels wide so it's
照片是2472像素宽，所以它
obviously a lot wider than the space
显然比空间宽得多
that it needs which is 214 too wide so
它需要是214太宽，以便
we can either crop and scale that we
我们可以裁剪和缩放我们
could copy it in paste it move it around
可以复制粘贴它移动它
like this kind of thing right and just
像这样的事情是对的，公正的
let it work like that and that's
让它像那样 那样 工作
probably how I would end up doing it in
可能我最终会怎么 做
some cases you may want to crop and
有些情况下你可能想裁剪和
scale your image itself first and see
首先缩放自己的图像，然后看看
what I've done is ctrl a ctrl C and then
我所做的是按ctrl c 然后
over this one I've hit control V to
在这一个我已经达到控制V
paste it in and then we'll let that be a
粘贴它，然后我们会让它成为一个
new layer so now this is perfect
现在这个新层是完美的
proportionately to that left area so
与左侧区域成比例
we'll move you around the canvas to
我们会将您移到画布上
where I like it and one of the things
我喜欢它和其中一件事
that I keep in mind here Hilary is that
我在这里记住希拉里就是这样
it's going to put this the pin hole at
它将把这个针孔放在
the top of the canvas as well so keep in
画布的顶部也是如此
mind that if you are doing full-size
请注意，如果你正在做全尺寸
picture yeah and the person is dead
图片是的，这个人已经死了
center they're gonna have a black dot
中心他们会有一个黑点
right there in the middle of their
就在他们的中间
forehead and that's where the pin is
额头，那就是针的位置
going to be right so so I try to
将会是正确的，所以我试着去做
position things in such a way that none
定位事物的方式是没有的
of the none of the foreground objects
没有任何前景物体
the people animals or a particular
人们的动物或一个特定的
focuses words if you've got text on your
如果你的文字有问题，请关注单词
images none of that stuff is going to be
图像没有这些东西 会
obscured by the by the hole ok good
被孔掩盖好了
thinking so similarly I know that the
我的思维非常类似，我知道
hole is going to be up right about here
洞在这里会是正确的
so it's not going to be in the middle of
所以它不会在中间
your hair or anything like that which
你的头发或任何类似的东西
would possibly look a little silly
可能看起来有点傻
so now I'm going to use a circular
所以现在我 要使用通告
ellipse marquee and I'm just going to
椭圆选框，我只是 要去
create a bit of a vignette on the photo
在照片上创建一些小插图
itself as well just to give it a nice
本身以及给它一个不错的
kind of look that looks a little more
看起来多一点的样子
professional than just a plain straight
专业而不仅仅是一个简单的直
off the camera picture with GIMP it's
用GIMP关闭相机图像
really easy because I can I can resize
真的很容易，因为我可以调整大小
my vignette once it's created and put it
我的小插曲一旦创建并放置它
exactly where I like it so I've created
正是我喜欢它的地方，所以我创造了
a around vignette I'm going to go select
我要去选择附近的小插曲
feather because this is 20 100 pixels
羽毛，因为这是 20 100像素
wide about 750 would be appropriate for
宽750左右将是适当的
this image you know about a quarter to
这个图像你知道 大约四分之一
half feathering and what that does it
一半羽毛和它是什么
doesn't look like it did anything i'm
看起来不像我做了什么
going to go select invert and then
去选择倒置，然后
create a new layer which is an empty
创建一个空的新图层
layer but i still have this marquee and
层，但我仍然 有这个选框和
now the marquee is outside of of you in
现在大帐篷在你之外
the image i'm going to go edit fill with
我要去的图像编辑填充
background color and see what that's
背景颜色，看看是什么
done whoo ok so it's created a really
完成了那么好，所以它创建了一个真正的
nice kind of mark you or a vignette so
好样的标志你或小插曲所以
now next step is I want to actually use
现在下一步是我想实际使用
this free form select tool and just kind
这个免费的表格选择工具，只是一种
of click around loosely around you
在你周围松散地点击
doesn't have to be exact by any means
不必 通过任何方式准确
because we're going to also feather this
因为我们也会这样做
one it's just so that we can brighten
只是为了我们可以照亮
you up and watch what's going to happen
你起来看看会发生什么
because the that feather is obviously
因为那羽很明显
covering part of you as well see how
涵盖你的一部分，以及如何
your darker yeah yeah okay so now I've
你的黑暗耶耶耶好，所以现在我已经
loosely gone around you i'm going to go
松散地走过你，我要走了
select and we're going to do a
选择，我们将做一个
feathering here but only about 250
羽毛在这里，但只有约250
pixels just so it's a soft edge and i'm
像素，所以它是一个软边， 我是
going to go control x okay and all
去控制x 好吧， 所有
that's done is just popped you right out
这完成了只是弹出你的权利
of that vignette so now that thing that
那个小插曲所以现在那件事
looks like that so where you are
看起来像那样，你在哪里
standing is perfectly empty would you
站立是完全空的你会
look at that I'm gonna put you back in
看看我会让 你回来
the photo and it looks like that so now
这张照片现在看起来就像这样
we'll file save as it's a little bit of
我们将文件保存为它的一点点
a gimp tutorial off hey unintentionally
一个吝啬的教程嘿无意
little learning so I'll just throw that
很少学习，所以我只会抛出
on the desktop and we'll call that photo
在桌面上，我们会给这张照片打电话
left jpg okay I'm going with JPEG
左jpg 好吧我要用JPEG
because I do want these files to be
因为我想这些文件是
under 10 megs if I was going with ping
如果我是用ping去的话，不到10兆
yes it would probably be higher quality
是的，它可能会更高质量
because it's lossless but then i'm going
因为它是无损的，但是我要走了
to have issues with the actual size of
与实际大小有关的问题
the images jpg because we're working in
因为我们在工作，图像jpg
fairly high resolution is still going to
相当高的分辨率仍将继续
be excellent you're not likely going to
非常好，你不可能去
be able to tell the difference so okay
能够分辨这种差异
so now I'm going to add images and
所以现在我要添加图像和
upload that new image from my desktop
从我的桌面上载新图像
photo left and you see that that is
照片留下，你看到那是
about five megs so does a good fair
大约五个大姆，所以一个公平的
sized file any questions in the chat
聊天中的任何问题
room so far Hillary is is there I am
到目前为止的房间希拉里是在那里我
here this is category 5 technology TV
这里是5类技术电视
and tonight we're looking at at Lulu and
今晚我们正在看露露和
we're creating our very own calendar you
我们正在创建我们自己的日历
can create your own custom calendar as
可以创建 自己的自定义日历
well using free tools such as what we're
以及使用免费工具，如我们的
using tonight for the image manipulation
今晚使用图像处理
end of it which is Kim and GIMP is
它是金和GIMP的结尾
available as a free download at gimp.org
可在gimp.org上免费下载
and then we're using the free online
然后我们使用免费的在线
tool called Lulu and it's available at
名为Lulu的工具，它可以在
lulu.com that's felt lu lu calm very
lulu.com那种感觉lu lu 很平静
cool there we go that's almost up I'm
在那里很酷我们走了，这几乎是我的
almost done questions in the chat room
几乎在聊天室里完成了问题
feel free to to ping us send them our
随时给我们发送我们的电子邮件
way here we go and while that's loading
在这里， 我们去的方式，而这是加载
I'm actually going to load the the next
我实际上会加载下一个
two files as well good thinking which we
两个文件以及我们的好思想
can do because it is multitask ok those
可以这样做，因为它是多任务 确定的
are the two there we go I say done so
是 两个我们走吧我说这样做
now this one is all loaded this is the
现在这一个是所有加载这是
one that we just created in the GIMP I'm
我刚刚在 GIMP中 创建的一个
going to grab that and drag it and pop
要 抓住这一点，拖动它和流行
it onto the left side there ok so you
它在左边那里没关系，所以你
can see that that is a perfect fit for
可以看出，这是一个完美的选择
that great the pinhole is as I said up
这个伟大的针孔是像我说的 了
to your left my right not on my noggin
在你的左边我的权利不在我的头上
no and it looks good on the brick there
不， 在那里的砖头上看起来不错
as well ok check on the status of our
以及检查 我们的状态
last two files it's about halfway done
最后两个文件大概完成了一半
question can finish calendar be sent
问题可以完成日历发送
anywhere around the world I believe so I
世界上任何地方我都相信我
mean Lulu is is an online ordering
意思露露是一个在线订购
system and you can make sense I've never
系统，你可以理解 我从来没有
heard of any able to limitations to
听说任何有能力的限制
where they can send to obviously your
他们可以发送给显然你的
shipping rates would vary depending on
运费根据不同而有所不同
where you live and
你住在哪里？
are they are being sent from but we
他们是从我们这里发出的吗？
don't see why not for sure and this one
不明白为什么不确定和这一个
is almost done here the month of March
几乎是在三月份完成的
so even though I'm you know those are
所以即使我知道那些是
still uploading I'm gonna hit save I
仍然在上传我会保存我
like to save my work we're gonna call
喜欢拯救我的工作，我们会打电话
this 2013 category 5 TV calendar cool
这2013年 5 类 电视日历很酷
author will just say Robbie Ferguson
作者只会说罗比弗格森
kisses it's but that is you I don't you
亲吻它，但那就是你我不是 你
know right now I'm gonna leave this
现在知道我要离开这个
private because I'm still working on I'm
私人的，因为我仍在为我工作
not gonna set it as public yet I'm gonna
不会将它设置为公开，但我会
hit save okay so now here's another
点击保存 好，现在这里是另一个
photo of you ready to go so I'm gonna
你准备好去的照片， 所以我会去的
drag that and drop it up here oh look at
拖动它并把它放在这里哦，看看
me give me with a little stuffed dog
我给了我一个小毛绒狗
yeah that was how that got into the
是的，那是怎么进入的
photo we'll never know I know I was like
照片， 我们永远不会知道我知道我是这样的
here take this stuff dawg i'm like i
这里拿这个东西dawg 我就像我
think is eric i think it was Eric push
想想是埃里克，我认为这是埃里克推
the puppy oh that seems like thank you
看起来像是感谢你的小狗哦
see ya it does seem like it doesn't last
看到它看起来 好像它不会持续
photo is just loading up here here comes
照片只是在这里加载
oh yeah that's me so now i can drag that
哦，那就是我，所以现在我可以拖动它
there and there it is okay so now we've
那里和那里现在好了，所以现在我们已经
got a Hillary collage so let's say I
得到了希拉里拼贴画，让我们说我
would prefer this to be reordered so I
我更喜欢这样重新排序
can actually drag this one down here and
实际上可以把这个拖到这里
drop it it will switch order I can move
放下它将切换我可以移动的命令
them back and forth depending on their
他们来回取决于他们的
dimensions I can zoom in and things like
尺寸我可以放大和类似的东西
that one of the nice things about this
这是关于这件事的好处之一
too is it is that Lulu is going to watch
露露也会去观看
out for the quality of your work so if
如果你的工作 质量 如此
for example let's say this left-most
例如，让我们说这 是最左边的
photo let's say we wanted to make you
照片让我们说， 我们想让你
just just a face shot right so we wanted
只是一张脸而已，所以我们想要
to zoom in so let's click on that and
放大，让我们点击那个 和
let's zoom in watch what happens at the
让我们放大看看会发生什么
top left okay warning yeah what's
左上角好吧，警告是啊
happening here is that ok you are
这里发生的事情就是你确定
actually exceeding the resolution of
实际上超出了决议
your photograph so if you've got a you
你的照片，所以如果你有你
know a particular photo and you try to
知道一个特定的照片，你尝试
stretch it out it's going to all of a
伸展出来它的将所有的
sudden step into
突然进入
ran great grainy looking photo right
跑了很大的粒状看照片的权利
because you're you're stretching it
因为你在伸展它
beyond the proportions of or the
超出比例或
dimensions of the image so that's
这是图像的尺寸
warning me that yeah you better you
警告我你是更好的你
better back up face is pixelated yes
更好的支持脸是像素化的
exactly there you go okay so that is the
就在那里，你会 好起来的，这样就是了
as far out as I would want to go and or
尽可能远离我想去或者
get a bit absolutely perfect resolution
得到一点绝对完美的决议
okay but we actually created this image
好吧，但我们实际上创造了这个形象
for this space so there are you and
对于这个空间，所以你和你
that's really all there is to it so
这真的就是这样
we've saved it once i'm going to save it
一旦我要保存它，我们就保存了它
again and now that we've made some
再次，现在我们已经做了一些
changes and when we're done so create
变化和我们完成时的创建
your cover create each individual month
你的封面创建每个月
huh we've only done done to today but
呵呵我们只做到今天，但是
let's pretend that we're ready to go now
让我们假装我们现在准备好了
we're gonna go preview and finish and it
我们要去预览并完成它
says you know obviously me it's warning
说你明明知道这是警告
me that I've got some n pages hey you
我知道我有几页，嘿，你
didn't do all the work you're supposed
没有做所有你应该做的工作
to do that's okay and there is the
做这没关系，有
Hillary page Wow so if you would like
希拉里页哇如果你愿意的话
that to grace your wall yeah let's get
那是为了让你的墙变得美好
real here let's jump over to July as
真正的这里让我们跳转到七月
well I want to show you something june
我想给你看6月的东西
july and the resolution is pretty low
7月份，分辨率相当低
here but you do see that there is some
在这里，但你确实看到有一些
writing on the screws yes indicating our
写在螺丝是指示我们
birth and that is our birthday so we can
出生，这是我们的生日，所以我们可以
go publish up at the top right and
在右上角发布
publish our calendar and now all of a
发布我们的日历，现在全部发布
sudden our calendar is is up ready to be
突然我们的日历是被东西准备是
ordered doesn't take very long at all
有序并不需要很长的时间
and so Lulu is going to go through those
所以Lulu将会通过这些
files create a print-ready version of
文件创建一个打印就绪版本
the file they're going to take care of
他们将要照顾的文件
the sales are going to take care of the
销售会照顾到
the actual order you know the order
您知道订单的实际订单
process they're going to provide you
他们将提供给你的过程
with a link that you can send to your
有一个你可以发送给你的链接
friends and it basically just goes
朋友，它基本上就是这样
through this process really really fast
通过这个过程真的很快
okay and they will let you know as soon
好吧 ，他们会 尽快 告诉你
as the the files are ready and you can
因为这些文件已准备就绪，你可以
start ordering your calendar so all in
开始订购您的日历，所有的东西
all I mean within you know and I you
我的意思是你内心深处，我是你
know you probably take an hour to do it
知道你可能需要一小时才能做到 这一点
right and you'd have a really
对，你会有一个真正的
nice-looking calendar so make sure your
好看的日历，所以确保你的
photos are as good a quality as you
照片和你一样好
possibly get like any print job you want
可能会像您想要的任何打印作业一样
them to be really high resolution if
他们如果真的是高分辨率的话
you're using a little chintzy camera not
你不是用一个小巧的相机
a good idea because it's going to result
一个好主意，因为它会导致结果
in
在
you know you're not going to be as happy
你知道你不会很高兴
with the with the results yeah if it's
与结果是啊，如果是的话
if it's low resolution so and that's
如果它的分辨率很低，那就是了
already done it's created for me I've
已经完成它为我创建了
got my downloadable version and I can
有我的可下载版本，我可以
actually save and continue and I can
实际上保存并继续，我可以
place an order my calendar is 1399 very
订购我的日历是1399非常
cool so in the event of us finishing
很酷，所以在我们完成的情况下
said caliber category five calendar yes
口径类别五日历是
oh it will be done to the general public
哦，它会对普通大众做
will be done they can order it yeah real
将完成他们可以命令它是真实的
you'll see it on real life category five
你会在真实生活类别五中看到它
TV if you'd like to have one of those
如果你喜欢电视有 那些 之一
for 2013 we've got pictures of the
对于2013年，我们已经有了照片
entire crew here at category 5
第5类的全体船员
technology TV season 6 so feel free i
科技电视第六季让我感到自由
mean go to category 5 TV we're gonna
意味着去5类电视，我们会去的
finish up our lulu calendar and make it
完成我们的 lulu日历并制作 完成
available to you also follow me on
提供给你也跟着我
twitter Ravi Ferguson follow Hillary on
叽叽喳喳拉维弗格森跟随希拉里
Twitter Hillary rumble follow the show
Twitter希拉里隆隆 声跟随节目
on Twitter its category 5 TV you see it
在Twitter上看到它的5类电视
down there just below Hillary and we're
在希拉里下面，我们是
going to be posting it there as soon as
将尽快发布在那里
it's ready for you and you can order it
它已经准备好了，你可以订购它
online direct from hulu very cool cool
网上直接来自hulu很酷很酷
and just an FYI category 5 TV is a
只是一个FYI 5类电视是一个
member of the tech podcast network if
科技播客网络的成员如果
it's tech it's fear and the
它的技术是恐惧和恐惧
international association of internet
国际互联网协会
broadcasters thanks oh you're welcome
广播公司感谢哦，不客气
ready fight I'm ready for the news are
准备好战斗我准备好 了新闻
you lot happening worldwide web
你很多事情发生在全球网络
happening in the world here it is comin
在这里发生的事情是这样的
atcha these are the top stories from
atcha这些是来自最新的故事
category 5 TV news room sir richard
第5类电视新闻室先生理查德
branson wanted to stay ship so to become
布兰森想保持这样的状态
a high-altitude science platform the
一个高空科学平台的
billionaire's rocket plane will carry
亿万富翁的火箭飞机将携带
six fare-paying passengers just above
六位乘客就在上面
the atmosphere to experience a few
气氛体验一下
minutes of weightlessness and to be
分钟的失重和 待
clear that's fair fa re not fair right a
清楚这是公平的不公平的权利a
fair price they have to pay a lot hey
公平的价格，他们必须支付很多嘿
sue that not fair an arm a leg seriously
严肃起诉那不公平的手臂
but you experience a few minutes of
但你经历了几分钟的 时间
weightlessness but the vehicle has been
失重，但车辆已经
designed so that its seats can be
旨在使其座椅可以
removed easily and the space then
然后轻松地移除空间
becomes filled with science gear
变得充满科学装备
passengers will ride the rocket plane
乘客将乘坐火箭飞机
for the fun of it but scientists would
为了它的乐趣，但科学家会
also use it for the same reasons they
也出于同样的原因使用它们
also fly experiments on the
也在上飞实验
International International Space
国际国际空间
Station or on sounding rockets to access
站或探空火箭进入
microgravity conditions very cool meet
微重力条件非常酷满足
the weightless environment provides a
无重力的环境提供了一个
unique perspective on physical systems
物理系统的独特视角
and processes and helping researchers
并处理和帮助研究人员
researchers to better understand disease
研究人员更好地了解疾病
and to develop new materials passenger
并开发新材料乘客
flights should begin in 18 months or so
航班应该在18个月左右开始
research sorties could start soon after
研究出发可能很快就会开始
that's awesome who knows how much
谁知道多少真棒
that'll cost but it sounds very cool
这会花费，但听起来很酷
moving along IBM says it has developed a
跟随IBM移动说它已经开发出了一个
chip that makes it easier to shuttle
芯片， 使其更容易穿梭
data via pitch or view pulses of light
通过俯仰或查看光脉冲数据
instead of using electrical signals the
而不是使用电信号
firm says it should offer a way to move
公司表示它应该提供一种移动方式
large amounts of information between
之间的大量信息
processors and computer servers at
处理器和计算机服务器
higher speeds than at present these
比目前这些更高的速度
provide computing power and data used by
提供使用的计算能力和数据
abs and other net services one third
abs和其他网络服务的三分之一
party expert said the significance of
党专家 说的意义
the innovation was that it was much
创新是很多
cheaper than other options details of
比其他选项更便宜的细节
the development are to be presented at
该发展将被呈现在
the International electron devices
国际电子设备
meeting in San Francisco hmm interesting
在旧金山开会很有意思
yesterday gmails outage was not just
昨天gmails中断不仅仅是
another pain out of control code also
另一个痛苦失控的代码也
brought down some
打倒了一些
browsers hurting productivity for those
浏览器会伤害这些人的生产力
affected as the boundary between cloud
作为云的边界受到影响
services and native clients for
服务和本地客户
enterprises cannot afford this kind of
企业买不起这种
instability any longer but it was not
不稳定，但事实并非如此
fun for if you are a google user for
如果你是谷歌用户，那么这很有趣
about 40 minutes yesterday afternoon on
昨天下午约40分钟
the east coast gmail service as well as
东海岸的gmail服务以及
Google Drive experienced scattered
Google云端硬盘遭遇分散
outages reports indicate that personal
停电报告显示个人
gmail accounts may have been affected
Gmail帐户可能已受到影响
more than the Google Apps account you
超过Google Apps帐户
know what's it what's wild about that is
知道这是什么是疯狂的
that people think well I don't use
人们认为我不会使用
Google maybe I use a different search
Google可能会使用其他搜索
engine that's why I'm not affected maybe
这就是为什么我不受影响的原因
I don't use Gmail or anything like that
我不使用Gmail或类似的东西
but Google and and all these different
但谷歌和所有这些 不同
cloud services are everywhere I mean if
云服务无处不在我的意思是如果
what actually happened to us if you can
如果 可以的 话，我们究竟发生了什么
believe Google's outage took out the
相信谷歌的停电已经消失了
category 5 website really yeah weird but
第5类网站真的很奇怪，但
how does that happen right they just own
这是怎么发生的，他们只是自己的
the world don't gay I'll show you how
世界不同性恋我会告诉你如何
this happened and you don't realize and
这发生了，你没有意识到
me as a program I'd never even thought
我作为一个我从未想过的程序
that yeah you know what well Google will
那是的，你知道Google会做得怎么样
have one day you know in December will
有一天你会知道12月份会
have an out intact so we'll take our
有一个完整的，所以我们将采取我们的
website you go to our website and there
网站你去我们的网站和 那里
it is and there's all our episodes and
它是和所有我们的情节和
everything you scroll down you take it
你向下滚动的所有东西都会带上它
for granted but all of a sudden you
这是理所当然的，但突然之间你会发现
realize so you know what there's a
意识到所以你知道有什么
calendar over here that shows you what's
日历在这里，显示你什么
coming up on the show that's powered by
即将推出的电视节目
our calendar on which is cool google
我们的日历很酷的谷歌
calendar right huh there it is would you
日历吧，那就是你了
look at that powered by google calendar
看看由谷歌日历驱动的
so this is where everything is stored so
所以这就是所有东西都存储的地方
what happened in our case it's trying to
我们正在试图发生的事情发生了什么
load the calendar and it ended up
加载日历并结束
failing out the website never loaded the
从未加载该网站失败
homepage so if you did see an error
首页，所以如果你 看到一个错误
message there during that Google outage
在那次谷歌停电期间发生的消息
that's what happened as soon as I caught
这就是我一发现就发生的事情
on to that I rewrote some code and made
为此我重写了一些代码并进行了编写
it so that there was an error handler
它有一个错误处理程序
there but a lot of people didn't realize
但有很多人没有意识到
and in our case because we cash the
在我们的情况下，因为我们兑现了
calendar so that is not making requests
日历，以便不发出请求
to Google all the time it basically
到Google一直基本上
connects out downloads the information
连接出下载信息
saves it on our server and then serves
将其保存在我们的服务器上，然后投放
it up to our viewers so that they're not
它取决于我们的观众，所以他们不是
actually making that connection because
实际上 是因为这样做
of that it was a cache file so even
它甚至是一个缓存文件
after you know they say well it was only
在你知道他们说得很好之后，它 只是
down for 30
下降30
answer it was only down for 40 minutes
回答只有40分钟
well we cash for ya a day so if I didn't
好吧，如果我没有，我们每天都会为你兑现
catch that and a lot of web yeah people
抓住那个和很多网络耶的人
won't be that proactive if I didn't
如果我没有那么积极主动
catch that the cash could have left our
赶上现金可能离开了我们的
website down for an entire day brother
网站下载一整天的兄弟
yeah so that's what they never would've
是的，所以这是他们永远不会有的
thought such as yeah they don't really
以为他们并不是真的
realize that know it affects a lot more
意识到知道它影响很多
than just you google users that are on
不仅仅是你谷歌是在用户
gmail yeah right absolutely huh got
Gmail是啊，绝对有权得到
another story for you peeps keeps on
另一个故事，你偷窥不断
coming the crazy this one affects me
来这个疯狂的人影响着我
personally oh no twitter has introduced
亲自哦，没有推出推特
a new feature allowing members to apply
一个允许成员申请的新功能
retro and other filters to their images
复古和其他过滤器到他们的图像
replicating instagram the popular
复制Instagram的流行
facebook own photography app which is
Facebook自己的摄影应用程序是
cut ties with the micro-blogging network
削减与微博网络的联系
the move is part of an effort by twitter
此举是Twitter推动的一部分
to take more control over its service it
更多地控制它的服务
has gradually restricted how much data
已经逐渐限制了多少数据
it shares with outside apps and
它与外部应用程序共享
introduced its own competing versions of
推出了自己的竞争版本
them thus you can see in the picture the
他们因此你可以在图片中看到
different layers and things you can add
不同的图层和你可以添加的东西
to your pictures the introduction of
给你的照片介绍一下
in-house image filtering software by
内部图像过滤软件
Twitter was anticipated last week
Twitter上周预计
Instagram severed a link with Twitter
Instagram切断了与Twitter的链接
cards a system that ensured photographs
卡片确保照片的系统
would be well presented if they were
如果是的话，会很好地呈现
shared on Twitter over the weekend it
在周末的Twitter上共享它
stopped its members embedding
阻止其成员嵌入
photographs and tweets completely
照片和推文完全
sharing an Instagram image now means a
分享Instagram图片现在意味着一个
link is posted hmmm ouch now I can't see
链接已发布hmmm ouch现在我 看不到
my Instagram pics well there'll be links
我的Instagram图片很好，会有链接
if you want that yeah that's interesting
如果你想这是有趣的
because Instagram used to be while I
因为Instagram曾经是我
mean twitpic what was the big thing and
这意味着什么是重大的事情
then Twitter went and created something
然后Twitter去创造了一些东西
to replace them and that was unfair that
以取代他们， 这是不公平的
was that was unnecessary but here is an
那是不必要的，但这里是一个
instance where Instagram was the one was
Instagram是其中的一个例子
for Twitter right and then all of a
Twitter的权利，然后所有的一个
sudden facebook bought it made it for
突然的facebook买了它
facebook and then shut down yeah its
Facebook，然后关闭是的
ability to use Twitter that's sneaky
使用 狡猾的Twitter的能力
sneaky so now hey your ego there's
现在偷偷摸摸，现在嘿，你的自我有
another option for it
另一个选择
um least the features haven't been lost
至少这些功能没有丢失
I yeah at least they're doing something
至少他们正在做一些事情
else that's true something their own
否则这是他们自己的事情
thing all right last story it may not
事儿没事儿最后的故事也可以不
look like a character from the
看起来 像一个人物
transformer franchise but a tiny robot
变压器专营权，但一个小小的机器人
made in the u.s. is able to change shape
在美国制造是能够改变形状的
built at the massachusetts institute of
建于马萨诸塞州的马萨诸塞州学院
technology MIT it uses magnets to mimic
技术MIT使用磁铁来模仿
molecules that fold themselves into
将自身折叠成分子的分子
complex shapes the research could lead
研究可能导致复杂的形状
to robots I could be reconfigured to
到机器人我可以重新配置
perform many different tasks the beard
执行许多不同的任务胡子
weird because I when you told us about
奇怪，因为我当你告诉我们
this I was kind of expecting something
这是我期待的东西
that could make itself look like a
这可能会使自己看起来像一个
hamburger or a sandwich not yet but this
汉堡或 三明治还没有，但这
looks more like a human chain link of
看起来更像是一个人类的链环节
metal we need a video when he see it
金属我们需要一个视频， 当他看到它
yeah maybe see it actually changing
是的，也许看到它实际上在变化
shape morphing yeah transform Autobots
形状变形耶变换汽车人
what do you think it's kind of like hey
你觉得这有点像嗨
so what else could it turn into maybe
那么还有什么可能变成可能
like a circle circular kind of version
像一个圆形的圆形版本
of itself but hey to start it is a start
本身， 但嘿启动它是一个开始
and that's it for the newsroom you can
这就是 新闻编辑室所能做到的
get these full stories online at
在线获取这些完整的故事
category 5 TV / newsroom the newsroom is
第5类电视/新闻编辑室
researched by roy w nash with
由罗伊w 纳什研究
contributions from our amazing community
我们惊人的社区贡献
of viewers if you have a story you
的观众，如果你有一个故事你
think's worthy of on-air mention shoot
认为值得在空中提及拍摄
us an email at category 5 or newsroom at
我们在第5类或新闻编辑室发送电子邮件
category 5 TV from the newsroom I'm
来自新闻编辑室的5类电视
Hillary rumble thanks health tonight's
希拉里隆隆感谢今晚的健康
show is brought to you in part by
节目是由你带来的一部分
quarter II electrical contracting inc
第二季度电气承包公司
find them online at quarter electric com
在季度电子公司网上找到他们
if you're looking for an electrician an
如果你正在寻找一名电工
electrical company anywhere in Simcoe
电气公司在Simcoe任何地方
County the surrounding areas make sure
县周边地区确保
you give them a call 705 326 to 179 also
你也给他们拨打电话705 326至179
we would love to give you a free one
我们很乐意给 你一个免费的
month trial of netflix cat5 TV / netflix
Netflix cat5 TV / netflix的月试用版
cool dude mm-hmm so hey you got some
酷帅哥嗯，所以嘿，你有一些
viewer questions for me I do all right I
观众对我的问题我做得很对
do I do thanks for sending your question
我要谢谢你发送你的问题
we love getting them because that's what
我们喜欢收到他们，因为那是什么
we love to do answer your questions help
我们喜欢回答你的问题帮助
you out this comes to us from Lewis from
你从刘易斯那里找到我们
Ireland see lewis dear robbie i have
爱尔兰见我有刘易斯亲爱的罗比
installed a version of ubuntu knoppix i
安装了ubuntu knoppix i的一个版本
call it the german version i find it
称之为德国版我发现它
very easy to use the computer details
非常容易使用电脑的细节
are athlon 750 dual processor
是athlon 750双处理器
the moment two gigabytes of memory but
当下两千兆字节的内存但是
by the time you read this we will have 8
当你阅读这个时，我们将有8个
gigabytes of memory the processor speed
千兆字节的内存处理器速度
is 2.7 gigahertz we have installed
我们已经安装了2.7千兆赫兹
VirtualBox and works okay but will not
VirtualBox和工作正常，但不会
recognize the USB port why can you tell
识别USB端口为什么你可以告诉
me how to solve this the USB port works
我如何解决这个USB 端口的作品
on Abu tube but does not seem to work on
在Abu 管上，但似乎没有工作
VirtualBox with Windows the computer has
与计算机的Windows VirtualBox
two extra cards that gives me extra USB
两个额外的卡，给我额外的USB
ports many thanks and um thanks for help
港口非常感谢，并感谢您的帮助
sure so kubuntu is the host yes I think
当然，所以kubuntu 是我认为的主人
and and windows is the guest on virtual
而且窗户是虚拟的客人
motley USB is a proprietary system and
杂色的USB是一个专有系统和
and so if you installed depending on how
所以如果你安装取决于如何
you install your virtual box is going to
您安装虚拟框会
determine whether or not you're able to
确定你是否是能
access USB so there's a couple of
访问USB，所以有几个
different ways now if you go into
现在不同的方式， 如果你进入
synaptic package manager and do an
突触包管理器并做一个
install a virtual box through that
通过它安装一个虚拟框
you're going to be getting what's called
你会 越来越什么叫做
the OSE or the open-source edition
OSE或开源版本
VirtualBox ok virtualbox OS e ok so that
VirtualBox确定virtualbox操作系统 确定
does not include USB support because it
不包括USB支持，因为它
is strictly open standard stuff so in
严格按照标准开放
order to get the USB support you need to
为了获得您需要的USB支持
have the full version of virtual box
有虚拟盒子的完整版本
which is available through their own
这是可以通过他们自己的
repositories which you can get on their
你可以在他们的资料库中找到它们
website virtualbox org and let's see
网站virtualbox组织，让我们看看
it's been a while since I've been here
自从我来到这里已经有一段时间了
but downloads over on the left hand side
但在左侧下载
scroll now let's click on VirtualBox for
现在滚动让我们点击VirtualBox for
linux hosts ok and you can either get
Linux主机好，你可以得到
the prepackaged stuff here I would
预先包装的东西， 我会的
scroll down here and actually get one of
向下滚动并实际获得其中一个
the Debian repositories get the one
Debian存储库获得了该版本
that's appropriate for your version of
这适合你的版本
ubuntu how you can determine that C
Ubuntu如何确定C
precise when Eric natty maverick lucid
准确的时候埃里克natty特立独行清醒
quick way now there's a couple different
快速的方式现在有一对夫妇不同
ways but let's go administrative system
方式，但让我们去行政系统
administration system monitor
管理系统监视器
system and you see that I am running
系统， 你看到我正在运行
Maddie okay so for me I will take that
麦迪没关系，对我来说，我会接受
line that has natty okay and i will copy
有natty 好行，我会复制
that to my clipboard and then i will go
那对我的剪贴板，然后我会去
into administration either synaptic
投入管理或突触
package manager or i can go into i can
包经理或我可以进去我可以
go into it directly but i'll do it
直接进入它， 但我会做到这一点
through synaptic package manager just so
通过突触包管理器就是如此
you can see that's probably where you'll
你可以看到那可能就是你想要的
install it from settings repositories
从设置存储库安装它
other software add and then paste in
其他软件添加， 然后粘贴
your apt line with ctrl v get rid of
你与ctrl v的适当的路线摆脱
that character that I got at the end
最后得到的那个角色
there if you get one like that and so
那里如果你得到那样的一个等等
that it just reads the text and then hit
它只是读取文本然后点击
add source and then you'll have that
添加源，然后你会有
source to be able to install the full
源码能够安装完整
version then you want to follow the
版本，那么你想 跟着
commands here just follow the
命令在这里只是按照
instructions it's pretty easy grab this
说明它很容易抓住这一点
line well you know what they've got a
行，你知道他们有什么
combined line here get this line here
这里组合的线在这里得到这条线
what this does is it gets the gpg key
这是做什么的， 它获得了gpg的关键
for their repository which sounds fancy
因为他们的存储库看起来很花哨
dancy what it means is it's going to
丹西它的意思是它要
prevent you getting errors because it's
防止你因为它而得到错误
it basically gives it gives your
它基本上给它给你的
computer the information to know that
电脑知道这些信息
this is a trusted repository so if you
这是一个可信任的存储库，所以如果你
copy that combined link and paste that
复制该组合链接并粘贴
into your terminal copy bring up a
进入你的终端副本带来了一个
terminal window there you go edit paste
终端窗口，你去编辑粘贴
and then hit enter it's going to
然后点击进入即可
actually download that key and it's
实际上下载该密钥，它是
going to add it so that you can now
将添加它，以便你现在可以
install without any problem follow the
安装没有任何问题
instructions there apt-get update and
有指示apt-get更新和
then install virtualbox dash 4.2 at this
然后在此处安装virtualbox dash 4.2
point on December 11 2012 okay so that
点12月11日2012年 好吧，以便
gives you the full version now we need
为您提供我们需要的完整版本
what's called the extension pack let's
所谓的扩展包让我们
see where we can find that downloads
看看我们在哪里可以找到下载
okay so we've got virtualbox installed
好吧，我们已经 安装 了 virtualbox
now let's pretend okay this is the next
现在让我们假装这是下一个
step Oracle VM VirtualBox okay I must
一步Oracle VM VirtualBox 好吧，我必须
have there it is okay cool
有在那里很酷
looking for the extensions there it is
寻找它的扩展
okay virtualbox extension pack release
好的virtualbox扩展包版本
for virtual box personal use evaluation
用于 虚拟箱子个人使用评估
VirtualBox older builds no don't want
VirtualBox的老版本不需要
that their builds oh here we go
他们的建筑哦，我们走吧
extension pack all supported platforms
扩展包所有支持的平台
right up at the top okay that extension
在顶端好吧，延长
pack in fact gives now virtual it sounds
实际上现在给了它虚拟的声音
all complicated but this is when Oracle
所有复杂但这是Oracle的时候
took over right virtualbox when they
他们接管了正确的virtualbox
bought out sun microsystems and took
买了太阳微系统，并采取了
over they broke everything up so now
他们现在打破了一切
it's it's a little more complicated off
这是一个 有点复杂关闭
the get-go but it's really actually
开始，但它确实是
quite a seamless way to do things so now
现在做的事情非常无缝
I've actually got that file okay so i
我其实已经有了这个文件，所以我
can copy that file it's from my
可以从我的文件复制该文件
downloads i can go into VirtualBox go
下载我可以进入VirtualBox去
file preferences extensions now you see
文件首选项扩展现在你看到
that I already have it but now I can
我已经拥有了它，但现在我可以
click on this fancy little thing over
点击这个奇特的小东西
here for add package and I can grab that
在这里添加包，我可以抓住它
file okay and then open it that's going
文件没问题然后打开它就行了
to give me the extension pack and that
给 我 扩展包和那个
extension pack now says I've got SATA
扩展包现在说我有SATA
support I've got USB support I've got
支持我有我得到的USB支持
all these different things that don't
所有这些不同的事情都没有
come with the free version of a virtual
附带虚拟的免费版本
box because they're not free as in
因为他们不是免费的
freedom so then you've got your Windows
自由，那么你有你的Windows
machine up and running with the
机器启动和运行
extension pack installed on VirtualBox
在VirtualBox上安装的扩展包
you need to hit devices and then install
你需要点击设备然后安装
guest additions even if you've already
即使你已经添加了客人
done it make sure you do it again it's
做到 了确保 你做 一遍它的
going to update you to the latest
要 更新到最新
version is going to give you support for
版本要给大家支持
all of the things that are supported but
所有支持的东西， 但
do be mindful that on your system here's
请注意，在你的系统上
a window system here i'm going to go
一个窗口系统，我要去了
settings now that you've got the
现在你已经有了设置
extension pack installed go to USB here
这里安装扩展包到USB
and just make sure that USB controller
并确保USB控制器
is enabled and USB 2.0 is enabled okay
启用和USB 2.0启用好吗
so that will ensure that your Windows
这样可以确保你的Windows
machine is in fact going to have access
机器实际上将有权访问
to your USB ports hmm all right good
到您的USB端口嗯没问题
luck hope that works out well for you
祝你好运，希望 对你有好处
let us know virtual box is amazing to
让我们知道虚拟框是惊人的
allow you to run multiple operating
允许您运行多个操作
systems on your computer gives you a
你电脑上的系统给你一个
good testing environment if you want to
良好的测试环境，如果你想
mess around with something in
在一些东西中乱七八糟
that you don't quite trust or if you
你不太 信任，或者如果你
just want to be able to clean things up
只是希望能够清理干净
really easily and revert them back to a
真的很容易，并恢复他们回到一个
previous state a virtual machine just
以前的状态只是一个虚拟机
makes it so easy breezy but it also
使它 容易凉风习习，但也是如此
allows you to use system resources to
允许您使用系统资源
their fullest extent because these days
因为这些日子最充分的程度
we've got such fast powerful computers
我们有这么快速的强大电脑
and it's wasted resources yeah you know
这是浪费你知道的资源
why do I have 16 gigs of RAM well let's
为什么我有16个RAM的演出呢？
run three more operating systems at the
运行三个以上的操作系统
same time as well I'll give them each
同时我也会给他们每个人
four gigs happy happy wow thanks very
四个演唱会开心快乐哇非常感谢
much for the question your question it's
很多问题是你的问题
flying by tonight ain't no only seven
今晚飞行不仅是 七个
minutes left of the show no lots of
节目还剩几分钟没有多少节目
questions but I have I have some
问题，但我有一些
questions of my own yeah what's up Wow
我自己的问题是怎么回事 哇
I'm wondering tis the season to be jolly
我想知道这个 季节是快乐的
where does one find music my Christmas
我的圣诞节在哪里找到音乐？
music for festivus how do i access the
音乐为festivus我如何访问
Christmas songs on the interwebs without
圣诞节歌曲在互联网上没有
paying a hefty fee because we love doing
支付高昂的费用，因为我们喜欢做
stuff for free and or inexpensively here
免费或在这里廉价的东西
on the shipping you and I have looked at
在你和我看过的航运上
you remember looking at shoutcast before
你还记得以前看过shoutcast
that's one of the first places that I
那是我的第一个地方之一
would drag I have a vague memory of that
会拖累我有一个模糊的记忆
yes ok this is cross-platform so if you
是的，好的，这是跨平台的，所以如果你
and it doesn't have to be Christmas
它不一定是圣诞节
music but if you're if you're interested
音乐，但如果你是如果你有兴趣
in Christmas music I'll just I am yeah
在圣诞音乐中，我只是我是的
and I am too but what I mean by that is
我也是，但我的意思是
there are there's every genre that you
那里有你的各种流派
could ever want ok alternative blues
可能想要 好的替代蓝调
country whatever so if that's what I
不管怎样，如果那就是我
mean when I say it doesn't have to be
意思是 当我说不必 是
Christmas this is shoutcast calm now
圣诞节现在是冷静的
what is this you think oh well this is
这是什么，你认为这是
just some website that's a whole bunch
只是一些网站，这是一大堆
of radio stations and that is completely
的广播电台，这是完全的
untrue shoutcast is a service provider
不真实的shoutcast是一个服务提供商
by nullsoft now do you remember nullsoft
现在您还记得nullsoft吗？
they're the creators of winamp and back
他们是winamp和后面的创造者
when internet radio was in its heyday
当互联网电台在其鼎盛时期
they created the you know the the winamp
他们创造了你知道 的 winamp
service and shoutcast the service to be
服务和shoutcast服务
able to stream they basically made it so
能够流他们基本上这样做
that radio stations could stream online
广播电台可以在线播出
so this is still in existence shoutcast
所以这仍然存在shoutcast
still exists and people still broadcast
仍然存在，人们仍然在播出
through the shoutcast servers so
通过shoutcast服务器如此
these are independent radio stations
这些是独立的广播电台
these are FM radio stations these are
这些都是调频广播电台
online only radio stations I love live
只有在线的广播电台我喜欢现场
Ireland which is a real Irish radio
爱尔兰是一个真正的爱尔兰电台
station from Dublin Ireland Ireland and
来自都柏林爱尔兰爱尔兰站
it's actually broadcasting from Dublin
它实际上是从都柏林广播
and Here I am a very and I can listen so
在这里，我是一个非常非常能听的人
for us tonight for for Christmas music
对于我们今晚的圣诞音乐
fest we can just click on seasonal &amp;
我们只需点击季节性＆
holiday at the left hand side well that
在左边的假期那么好
was easy easy crazy and there are you
很容易容易发疯，并且有你
know a ton of different stations to
知道一大堆不同的电台
choose from show more you know it just
选择展现更多你只知道它
keeps going and going and going and
继续前进 和前进
you'll find which ones you like the most
你会发现你最喜欢哪一个
you'll notice that they're sorted by
你会注意到他们按照排序
listener and and quite often time you'll
倾听者， 而且经常会有时间
find that the more listeners generally
发现一般听众越多
speaking the better the quality of the
说更好的质量
radio station you're not going to see
广播电台，你不会看到
one of the real chintzy radio stations
真正的chintzy广播电台之一
with with one or two listeners right so
与一个或两个听众合适
got radio Christmas celebration for
得到广播圣诞节庆祝
example it's broadcasting at only 64
例如它仅在64位播出
bits per second probably kilobits per
每秒的比特数可能是每千比特
second per me so half of CD quality as
第二我每个人的CD质量的一半
far as mp3 is concerned but it is a AC
就mp3而言， 但它是一个AC
so that means it's going to actually be
所以这意味着它实际上会是
really good quality sound this one here
这里真的很好的音质
this is got radio Christmas celebration
这是广播圣诞节的庆祝活动
it's broadcasting 128 bits kilobits per
它每个广播128位千比特
second mp3 so this is similar to CD
第二个MP3，所以这是类似于CD
quality so you're actually listening to
质量，所以你实际上在听
this thing at close to CD quality both
这件事情接近CD品质
of these right so if I click on the play
这些权利，所以如果我点击播放
button next to one of them it's simply
按钮旁边的按钮很简单
going to now this one downloaded a pls
现在这个下载了一个请求
file because my linux system is set to
文件，因为我的Linux系统设置为
open pls files in movie player just
只需在电影播放器​​中打开文件
totem and that's fine that's how i would
图腾，这很好， 我就是这样
so there you go okay so that's one
所以你会好起来的，所以这是一个
station if you're not happy with that
如果你不满意的话
one click on the next one it's all free
点击下一个就可以免费
oh that's the same one it's the same
哦，那是一样的
radio station that's that's right just
广播电台这是正确的
two different versions so whichever one
两个不同的版本，无论哪一个
you think sounds nicer so next one you
你认为听起来更好，所以下一个你
know let's say okay we were more into
知道让我们说好吧，我们更深入
the inspirational classics this one's
这是励志经典
playing silent night right now yeah
现在是玩沉默的夜晚
gusta carols yeah so there there are all
古斯塔颂扬耶，所以那里有所有
these options and then of course when
这些选项，当然当然
it's over when Christmas is over you
圣诞节结束时你已经结束了
head on over to the country stations
前往国家电台
here and you can click on kickin country
在这里，你可以点击kickin国家
and taking caltrain you know if that
然后服用Caltrain，你知道这是否
wasn't a country split second clip that
不是一个国家分裂的第二个剪辑
I don't know what what a better
我不知道什么是更好的
personifies country than that yeah so
更像是这样的国家
that's shoutcast calm for christmas
这对圣诞节来说是冷静的
music it's it's simply seasonal &amp;
音乐，它只是季节性＆
holiday on the left-hand side check it
在左边的假期检查它
out that was easy absolutely free and it
这很容易完全免费，它
has that ability to play directly within
有直接在内玩的能力
your browser by default so that even if
即使你的浏览器默认
you don't have a player like totem
你没有像图腾这样的球员
installed you can still listen if you
如果你安装，你仍然可以听
want to change those settings go up to
想要更改这些设置
help and settings you do not need to
帮助和设置你不需要
create an account by default it's going
默认情况下 创建一个帐户
to be just the web player which is cool
只是网络播放器很酷
and that's going to that's going to do
这就是要做的
pretty well for you what I mean by you
非常好为你做什么我的 你 的意思
don't have to create an account when you
当你不必创建一个帐户
when you usually when you go to a
当你平时当你去的时候
website that allows you to save settings
网站，允许您 保存设置
it requires a login and a password and
它需要一个登录名和一个密码
given them personal information there's
给他们个人信息
none of that on shoutcast instead they
这些都不是shoutcast而是他们
just use a cookie so if you clear your
只要使用一个饼干，所以如果你清除你的
browser cache you're gonna lose your
浏览器缓存你会失去你的
settings and just have to reset them
设置，只需重置它们
again but that's all fine and dandy and
再一次，但这一切都很好，很棒，而且
private mmm good stuff cool thank you
私人嗯好东西很酷谢谢你
for sharing that cuz i know i was
因为我知道我是因为 分享 那个cuz
curious and i am I vaguely remembered
好奇， 我依稀记得
this setup I couldn't remember the
这个设置我不记得了
website if you're on Android as well if
网站，如果你在Android上，以及如果
you've got an android phone or android
你有一个android手机或android
android tablet you install the winamp
安卓平板电脑安装winamp
app that will give you access to
应用程序，可以让你访问
shoutcast if you're on iOS iphone or
如果你使用的是iPhone或iPhone，就应该使用shoutcast
ipad there is actually an app called
iPad 实际上有一个应用程序叫
shoutcast so by the roar so when app on
所以在应用程序上时，吼叫就是如此
android shoutcast on iOS and you'll have
在iOS上的Android shoutcast，你 会有
access to that entire repository that
访问整个存储库
entire list of radio stations including
包括无线电台在内的整个列表
the chris
克里斯
stuff hey like that thank you fabulous
东西嘿喜欢，谢谢你神话般的
this is category 5 technology TV can't
这是5类技术电视无法做到的
believe how time is flying by tonight
相信今晚的时间飞逝
always flies when you're having fun have
当你玩得很开心的时候总会过得很快
fun here on show yes hey chat room don't
在这里展示的乐趣是嘿聊天室不
forget we've got lots of stuff to give
忘记我们有很多东西要捐献
away for Christmas we've got our
过圣诞节我们有我们的
Christmas specials I'm not very very
圣诞特价我不是很特别
excited about that and it's it's been a
对此感到兴奋，这是一个
lot of work getting ready for it so I
很多工作正在为此做好准备
hope that you can join us it's going to
希望你能加入我们的行列
be broadcasting at the same time as ever
与以往同时播出
but on Christmas Day because Tuesday is
但在圣诞节那天是因为周二
Christmas so we'll actually be
圣诞节， 所以我们真的会
broadcasting our live show hey Dennis
广播我们的现场表演嘿丹尼斯
John so it's it's gonna be a lot of fun
约翰如此，这将会很有趣
and what is happening that's a little
发生了什么，这是一点点
bit different with our Christmas special
与我们的圣诞节特别有点不同
I don't want to give anything away but
我不想放弃任何东西，但是
let's just say if you're into some music
让我们只是说，如果你进入一些音乐
you won't need to go to show cast not it
你不需要去演出就不会
at all that's all I'm saying ok we also
尽管如此，我只是说我们也是
have we've got that printer to give away
我们有没有打印机可以放弃
which we're going to be reviewing next
我们将在下面进行审查
week's going to be talking about that
本周将 讨论这个问题
that will be given away during our
这将在我们的期间给予
Christmas special also we have packs of
圣诞节特别也有我们的包装
batteries from ecole alkalines check
来自ecole alkalines检查的电池
them out Eco alkalines calm and that
他们出于生态碱冷静和那
we've got I believe six kind of packages
我们有我相信六种包装
of batteries that we're going to be not
的电池，我们将不会
not individual packs but Lee oh yes of
不是单独的包装，而是Lee哦，是的
batteries in it you'll get an assortment
电池里面你会得到一个分类
of batteries so yeah and lots of other
电池，所以是和其他很多
stuff as well so don't miss it it's
东西以及所以不要错过它
gonna be awesome and yeah Bobby what's
会是真棒，是啊鲍比是什么
tomorrow quickly what's special about
明天很快有什么特别的
tomorrow oh yes thanks hill no foul I
明天哦，是的， 谢谢山没有犯规我
was 12 12 12 and at 12 well in the
是12 12 12和12
afternoon I expect everyone to be
下午我希望每个人都是
tweeting and retweeting each other oh
互相推送和转发哦
it's kind of the last time that that's
这是最后一次
gonna happen for a while right I mean I
会发生一段时间我的意思是我
guess we'll be all binary some time to
猜猜我们会在一段时间内完成二进制
consuming I mean we've got to go through
消耗我的意思是我们必须经历
another hundred years to get there so
再过百年如此
that's kind of a big deal alright have a
这是一个很大的 好处有一个
a wonderful night um yeah and really
一个美妙的夜晚嗯是的，真的
looking forward to what's to come over
期待将要发生的事情
the next couple of weeks Heather thanks
接下来的几周希瑟谢谢
for being here again tonight fabulous
因为今晚再次来到这里
photog
photog
yes check out our Facebook web page fill
是检查我们的Facebook 网页填写
it as well on our website category 5 TV
它也在我们的网站类别5电视上播放
click on the facebook link and Heather
点击facebook链接和希瑟
is here shooting some behind the scenes
在这里拍摄一些幕后
and and some really cool stuff there
还有一些非常酷的东西
that you don't normally get to see and
你 通常不会看到和
that all gets posted to Facebook so
所有这些都发布到Facebook
happy yeah check it out get out make
开心耶检查它 出去化妆
sure you suck us on Facebook as well
当然你也可以在Facebook上吸引我们
that's important to us it makes us feel
这对我们很重要，它让我们感觉到
a warm and fuzzy inside it they really
一个温暖和模糊 里面 他们 真的
like us like this my place oh thanks for
像我们这样的我的地方哦谢谢
being here take care bye everybody next
然后在这里关心大家
Tuesday and Sasha dear mantis will be
星期二和萨沙亲爱的螳螂会
here next Tuesday night
下周二晚上
we hope you enjoyed the show category 5
我们希望你喜欢这个节目类别5
TV broadcast live from Barrie Ontario
电视直播来自巴里安大略省
Canada every tuesday at seven pm eastern
加拿大每星期二晚上七点在东部
if you're watching this on demand or
如果你正在观看这个需求或
through cable TV check out the local
通过有线电视检查当地
show times in your area at category 5 TV
在您所在地区的 5 类 电视节目中播放时间
and find out when you can watch live and
并找出你什么时候可以观看现场直播
interact in the community chat where
在社区聊天中进行交互
category 5 is a production of prodigy
5类是神童的产物
digital solutions and is licensed under
数字解决方案并获得许可
creative commons attribution 2.5 canada
创意共用归属地2.5加拿大
we'll see you next time thanks for
我们会在下次谢谢你的时候见到你
tuning in
在调整